E=mc²
Young Einstein is a comedy, science fiction film directed by Yahoo Serious.
Albert Einstein is the son of a Tasmanian apple farmer, who discovers the secret
of splitting the beer atom to put the bubbles back into beer.
When Albert travels to Sydney to patent his invention he meets beatuiful French scientist Marie Curie, as well
as several unscrupulous types who try to take advantage of the naive genius and his invention.
Albert Einstein, played by Yahoo Serious.
Marie Curie, played by Odile Le Clezio.
Mr. Einstein, played by Ian "Peewee" Wilson.
Mrs. Einstein, played by Su Cruickshank.
Preston Preston, played by John Howard.
Darwin's Bodyguard, played by Christian Manon.
Young Einstein is a 1988 Australian comedy film written,
produced, directed by and starring Yahoo Serious.
It is a fantasized account of the life of Albert Einstein which alters all people, places and circumstances of his life, including relocating
the theoretical physicist to Australia, having him splitting the atom with a chisel, and inventing rock and roll and surfing.
Although highly successful in Australia, and winning an award from the Australian Film
Institute Awards, it was poorly received by critics in the United States.
At the APRA Music Awards of 1990, the soundtrack won
Most Performed Australasian Work for Film.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, atomic bomb,
nobel prize, marie curie, tasmanian.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.